LUKE BAILEY

Phone: 0492874856

lukejbailey2014@gmail.com

14/37 Hope Street, South Yarra, VIC 3141

ABOUT ME

I'm a friendly, focused, and inquisitive Cybersecurity Student with a passion for software development. I work well both alone and as part of a team, and thoroughly enjoy problem solving both in the workplace and in my free time.

On a more personal level, I love gaming, I speak Spanish as a second language, and have been a self-taught guitarist for over 20 years.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript: ES6, ES7, Node, React, JSX, Front End Web Development: HTML, CSS

Redux

Dev Ops: Git, GitHub, Docker, Debian Other Languages: Python, C, Bash, SQL

Applications: Excel, Word, PowerPoint Other Skills: Project Management, Strong

Communication, Pair Programming

EDUCATION

Advanced CertificateCybersecurityAugust 2022 - PresentCert IVCybersecurityAugust 2021 - June 2022

BSc (Hons) 2.2 Music Technology 2010 - 2014

EMPLOYMENT

1800GJ February 2020 - Present

Truck team Member

Direct Line Group January 2019 – December 2019

EVO consultant

Direct Line Group January 2017 – December 2018

Landlord & Tradesmen Consultant